<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<geophysical>
 <product>
         <product_title>Lipmann IP Earth Resistivity Meter</product_title>
		 <product_image>Lipmann IP Earth Resistivity Meter.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info><p>Our high resolution earth resistivity meter <strong>4point light 10W</strong> provides quantitative information about induced polarity (IP) of the soil. It measures the phase shift between the current injected into the ground and the voltage seen at the potential electrodes. It has adequate power to drive <strong>Schlumberger soundings up to L/2 = 1000 m</strong>.</p>
<strong>Application</strong>
<ul>
<li>Groundwater prospecting</li>
<li>Mining</li>
<li>Environment</li>
<li>Induced polarization</li>
<li>Near surface geophysics</li>
<li>Lab measurements</li>
<li>Examination of building materials</li>
<li>Archeology</li>
</ul></product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	   <product>
         <product_title>Ground Water Measurement</product_title>
		 <product_image>Ground Water Measurement.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info><p>Surface magnetic resonance (also known as surface NMR, proton magnetic resonance and magnetic resonance sounding) is a powerful ground-based geophysical method used to non-invasively detect, measure and image groundwater.</p>
<p>GMR™ instruments provide exceptional value for groundwater investigations due to their unique capabilities:</p>
<ul>
<li>GMR is the ONLY non-invasive geophysical method that can directly detect and image groundwater from the surface</li>
<li>GMR directly quantifies volumetric water content</li>
<li>GMR unambiguously differentiates moveable water in large pores from immoveable water that bound in small pores</li>
<li>GMR provides unambiguous estimates of hydrogeologic properties, including hydraulic conductivity and specific yield</li>
<li>GMR provides high vertical resolution of the hydrogeologic properties described above, to depths of up to 500 feet (150 meters)</li>
</ul></product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	   <product>
         <product_title>Ground Penetrating Radar</product_title>
		 <product_image>Ground Penetrating Radar.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info><p>Geophysical ground penetrating radar applications often relies on the depth penetration capabilities of low frequency antenna. Low frequency antennas enable greater depth penetration to determine bedrock compositions beneath the soil.</p>
<p>To create more meaningful datasets, geophysical professionals require GPS integration with their locating systems. To help streamline this process, all US Radar products can integrate with major GPS providers.</p>
<strong>GPR Can Also be Used to Locate:</strong>
<ul>
<li>Density changes</li>
<li>Fill placement</li>
<li>Boulders and rocks</li>
<li>Root mass</li>
<li>Disturbed soil</li>
<li>Buried wood</li>
</ul></product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	   <product>
         <product_title>Seismometer</product_title>
		 <product_image>Gerobit.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info><p>Our involvement with Geophysical &amp; Seismological Instruments starts at the early 2000's as instrument designers and field support for micro-seismic monitoring companies. We have designed and manufactured several types of seismic monitoring instruments, focusing in low cost, easy of use, very low power consumption and high reliability. Our instruments have been used in hundreds at projects in the most difficult conditions and harsh environments, worldwide, We are more than happy that they never had any operational problem or fail. More than 2.650 instruments have been deployed worldwide up to now.<br /> <br /> Our company bears all the accumulated experience of the past years, broadens its activities into new seismic monitoring applications and launches commercial co operations as well as new products in the geophysical / seismological sector.</p></product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	  <product>
         <product_title>Magnetic Resonance Borehole Logging</product_title>
		 <product_image>Magnetic Resonance Borehole Logging.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info><p>Advanced Javelin family of borehole NMR magnetic resonance logging tools provide direct, low-cost, high-resolution measurements of hydrogeological properties that users really care about, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Volumetric water content</li>
<li>Pore size distribution</li>
<li>Bound and mobile porosity</li>
<li>Hydraulic conductivity</li>
<li>Transmissivity</li>
</ul>
<p>A single Javelin NMR log can provide all of these key hydrogeological properties at vertical resolution on the order of 25 to 50 centimeters, enabling unambiguous and precise characterization of the water storage and pore structure characteristics of any earth formations.</p></product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	   <product>
         <product_title>NMR Solutions for Soil and Core</product_title>
		 <product_image>NMR Solutions.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info><p>Man-portable NMR tools enable direct measurement of volumetric water content and high-resolution pore-scale analysis of soils, sediments and core samples. These tools are all man-portable and designed for use in the field.</p>
<ul>
<li>The Helios™ Soil and Core Sample Analyzer enables measurement of a wide range of soil and core samples, with diameters up to 4 inches, and with a unique combination of short echo spacing, wide bandwidth and low static field strength to mitigate the effects of magnetically susceptible rocks and soils</li>
<li>The Discus™ sensor provides rapid, non-invasive measurement of near surface soil moisture content, with the ability to profile water content in four separate depth zones ranging from 1 inch to 8 inches (2.5 to 20 cm). The Discus uses a battery-powered NMR control unit, that can be carried in one hand and operated outdoors in all weather conditions</li>
</ul>
<p>These man-portable instruments provide direct, low-cost, high-resolution measurements of hydrogeological properties that users really care about, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Volumetric water content</li>
<li>Pore size distribution</li>
<li>Bound and mobile porosity</li>
<li>Hydraulic conductivity</li>
<li>Transmissivity</li>
</ul>
<p>A single NMR log can provide all of these key hydrogeological properties at vertical resolution on the order of 25 to 50 centimeters (10 to 20 inches), enabling unambiguous and precise characterization of the water storage and pore structure characteristics of any earth formations.</p></product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
 <product>
         <product_title>Portable Borehole Logger - 6 SERIES (1000M / 500M / 600M CABLE)</product_title>
		 <product_image>6 SERIES (1000M_500M_600M CABLE).jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info>The 6 Series logging systems are our highest performance portable loggers with maximum depth capability and a number of significant operational features. Available configurations include the 600 DL as a six hundred meter single conductor system, 6B-1K as a one thousand meter system or GVX4 as a five hundred meter four conductor system capable of running borehole video as well as geophysical logs. All 6 Series logging systems are shock mounted in a compact, rugged MIL spec. case for transport and storage. All components are constructed entirely from aluminum, stainless steel and corrosion resistant materials. All appropriate surfaces are powdercoated or anodized.</product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	   <product>
         <product_title>Portable Borehole Logger - 3 SERIES (300M CABLE)</product_title>
		 <product_image>3 SERIES (300M CABLE).jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info>Our most popular logger, this very compact, highly refined, versatile device is in use around the world. Its highly durable design, optimal size and ease of use make it truly unique among commercially available portable borehole loggers. The 3 Series loggers are self- contained with the winch assembly integrated with the uphole power supply, winch motor controller, backlit digital depth and speed indicators and USB compatible PC interface. The 3 Series runs under the supplied DELogger software with data output stored in the LAS format.</product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	   <product>
         <product_title>Portable Borehole Logger - 1 SERIES (150M / 250M CABLE)</product_title>
		 <product_image>1 SERIES (150M_250M CABLE).jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info>The 1 Series set a new standard for value, refined simplicity, versatility and performance in portable borehole loggers/ well logging systems. They are unequaled among commercially available portable logging systems for the economical and precise exploration of water wells and other drill holes. Completely self contained, Hand Cranked, Light weight, Disc Brake with uni-directional clutch</product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	   <product>
         <product_title>Borehole Probes - Spectral Gamma Prob</product_title>
		 <product_image>Spectral Gamma Prob.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info>Measurement Range of Three channel (K, U, Th) plus total count gamma spectrometer Diameter is Ø40.0mm (1.57″) Length is 1200mm (47.2″) Weight is  3.5Kg (7.7Lb) Pressure Rating is 22.7MPa (3300PSI) Operating Temperature is 0º to 70ºC (32º to 158ºF) </product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	   <product>
         <product_title>Borehole Probes - Fluid Temperature Resistivity/Conductivity</product_title>
		 <product_image>Fluid Temperature ResistivityConductivity.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info>Measurement Ranges are   Fluid Resistivity: 0 to 200 ohm-M, Fluid Conductivity: 0 – 50000uS, Fluid Temperature: -5o to 60ooC (23o to 140oF) Temperature resolution: 0.01oC. Diameter is 41.3mm (1.63″), Length is 1240mm (48.8″), Weight is 4.1Kg (9Lb), Pressure Rating is 30.3MPa (4400PSI), Operating Temperature is -20o to 60oC (-4o to 140oF) </product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	   <product>
         <product_title>Borehole Probes - Gamma Probe</product_title>
		 <product_image>Gamma Probe.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info>Measurement Range is Natural Gamma: 0 to 100K CPS. Diameter is 41.3mm (1.63″), Length is  1000mm (39.4″), Weight is  3.6Kg (8Lb), Pressure Rating is 30.3MPa (4400PSI), Operating Temperature is  -20o to 60oC (-4o to 140oF) </product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	   <product>
         <product_title>Borehole Probes - Borehole Caliper</product_title>
		 <product_image>Borehole Caliper.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info>Measurement Range is Hole Diameter: 50.8mm – 356mm (2″ – 14″), Diameter is 41.3mm (1.63″), Length is  1499mm (59.0″), Weight is  7Kg (15.4Lb), Pressure Rating is  30.3MPa (4400PSI), Operating Temperature is  -20o to 60oC (-4o to 140oF)</product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	  <product>
         <product_title>Borehole Probes - Compact Combination Gamma/Electric probe</product_title>
		 <product_image>Compact Combination Gamma_Electric probe.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info><p>Measurement Range : Natural Gamma: 0 to 100K CPS (Ø1.0″ x 3.0″)
Self Potential: ±2000mV 16″ Normal Resistivity: 0 to 5000 ohm-M
Single Point Resistivity: 0 to 5000 ohms.</p>

<p>Diameter is Ø44.5mm (1.75″) Length is 916mm (36.1″) Weight is 3.6Kg (7.9Lb) Pressure Rating is 30.3MPa (4400PSI) Operating Temperature is -20º to 60ºC (-4º to 140ºF)</p>
</product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
      <product>
         <product_title>Geo Prediction Software - RokDoc Solution</product_title>
		 <product_image>Rockdoc.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info>RokDoc places powerful, sophisticated tools at your fingertips – all on a single, easy-to-use platform. It integrates geological, geophysical and engineering data to enable interdisciplinary analysis, using workflows and automated QC procedures. RokDoc gives you more confidence in the data and subsurface decisions.</product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	  <product>
         <product_title>Geo Prediction Software - Rock Physics</product_title>
         <product_image>RockPhysics.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info><p>Pan India offers Ikon Science's Rock Physics module lets both generalists and experts quickly and easily explore hundreds of geological scenarios to investigate the seismic response in both conventional and unconventional plays. Intuitive and powerful, the module features sophisticated rock physics, 2D modelling and well to seismic tie solutions. It seamlessly combines core, log and seismic data into predictive models to ensure your team makes better and faster investment decisions with more confidence.</p>
<p>Additional Rock Physics Enhancements</p>
<ul>
<li>Anisotropy</li>
<li>Attrimod</li>
<li>Advanced Well- Tie</li>
<li>VSP</li>
</ul>
</product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	  <product>
         <product_title>Geo Prediction Software - Rock Characteristic</product_title>
         <product_image>RockChar.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info><p>Determine the spatial and temporal rock and fluid distributions from exploration to production by combining 3D and 4D seismic data with powerful rock physics-enabled seismic reservoir characterization. Your team can easily define interactive, shared earth models that allow the integration of geophysical, geological and engineering data using powerful rock physics. Reservoir Characterization operates in both time and depth, producing rich descriptions of the subsurface to accurately determine risks.</p>
<p>Additional Rock Characteristic Enhancements</p>
<ul>
<li>SDC Inversion</li>
<li>Advanced SDC</li>
<li>Ji-Fi (Joint Impedance and Facies Inversion)</li>
<li>Reservoir Monitoring</li>
</ul></product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	  <product>
         <product_title>Geo Prediction Software - Pressure Prediction</product_title>
		 <product_image>PressurePre.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info><p>Establish the distribution of pore pressure and stress in the subsurface, understand pressure distribution and the geological basis for the development of overpressure with Ikon's Pressure Prediction module. It effectively analyzes direct and indirect (mudweights) pressure measurements, and allows you build and calibrate pore pressure models Your team can easily assess drilling data, image logs and lab data, as well as link dynamic and static measurements to determine stress regimes and interpret historical drilling and production performance. It combines geopressure and geomechanical models with 3D elastic properties to understand risk and estimate and forecast drilling and production performance at undrilled leads and prospects across the drilling portfolio.<br /><br/>Additional Pressure Prediction Enhancements</p>
<ul>
<li>Geomechanics and Image Logs</li>
<li>Seismic Pressure Calculator</li>
</ul></product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
	  <product>
         <product_title>Geo Prediction Software - IPOINT</product_title>
		 <product_image>IPOINT.jpg</product_image>
		 <product_info>iPoint provides a single home for all wellbore data, regardless of source or type. Preserve the information that’s important to your organization in a familiar manner, encouraging adoption and utilization across your teams.</product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
 
	  
</geophysical>

 <!-- 
      <product>
         <product_title></product_title>
		 <product_image></product_image>
		 <product_info></product_info>
         <product_document></product_document>
      </product>
    -->
